Don Walker Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 28-131)
  - Show Music (Box 28-91, 107-126)
    - On your toes, 1954 revival, Music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Glad to be unhappy, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 83/1)
      - The heart is quicker than the eye, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 83/2)
      - The heart is quicker than the eye dance, Condensed score (Box-folder 83/3)
      - It's got to be love, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 83/4)
      - Slaughter on tenth avenue, Piano score (Box-folder 83/5)
      - Too good for the average man, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 83/6)
      - You took advantage of me, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 122/16)
    - Out of the blues, 1933, Music by Charles Gilpin, lyrics by Joseph F. Follmann, Jr.; Mask and Wig Club show at the University of Pennsylvania
      - Full scores
        - Camille dance (Box-folder 83/8)
        - Dream sequence (Box-folder 83/9)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 83/10)
        - Hymn of donts (Box-folder 83/11)
        - Jig-saw jag dance and vocal (Box-folder 83/12)
        - Leave all your selling to Sam (Box-folder 83/13)
        - Oh! Camille (Box-folder 83/14)
        - On our way to meeting (Box-folder 83/15)
        - On with the show (Box-folder 83/16)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 83/17)
        - Pilgrim dance (Box-folder 83/18)
        - Puzzle picture (Box-folder 83/19)
        - Since Cupid paid me a call (Box-folder 83/20)
        - Step out of the blues dance and vocal (Box-folder 83/21)
        - A sweet to a sweet (Box-folder 83/22)
        - Sweets dance (Box-folder 83/23)
        - Tell me not dance and vocal (Box-folder 83/24)
        - The torch song (Box-folder 83/25)
        - Up in Camille's room (Box-folder 83/26)
        - We want Camille (Box-folder 84/1)
        - What's the use of waiting? (Box-folder 84/2)
        - When I am Burgomaster (Box-folder 84/3)
        - Vocal selection, Titles include: A sweet to a sweet; The honeymoon express; The hotsy totsy jingle; When I am a Burgomaster; Step out of the blues; Jig saw jag (Box-folder 84/1)
    - Pajama game, 1954, Music and lyrics by Richard Adler and Jerry Ross
      - Full scores
        - Entr'acte (Box-folder 123/1)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 123/2)
        - Her is (Box-folder 123/3)
        - Her is dance (Box-folder 123/3)
        - Her is reprise (Box-folder 123/3)
        - Hernando's hideaway (Box-folder 123/4)
        - Hey there (Box-folder 123/5)
        - Hey there incidental (Box-folder 123/5)
        - Hey there reprise (Box-folder 123/5)
        - I'll never be jealous again (Box-folder 123/6)
        - I'll never be jealous ballet (Box-folder 123/7)
        - I'm not at all in love (Box-folder 123/8)
        - I'm not at all in love change (Box-folder 123/8)
        - I'm not at all in love incidental (Box-folder 123/8)
        - Liebchen (Box-folder 123/9)
        - Montage, Laid in: piano-conductor score (Box-folder 123/10)
        - A new town is a blue town (Box-folder 123/11)
        - Once-a-year day (Box-folder 123/12)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 123/13)
        - Pajama game closing (Box-folder 123/14)
        - Pajama game opening (Box-folder 123/15)
        - Racing with the clock (Box-folder 123/16)
        - Racing with the clock reprise (Box-folder 123/16)
        - Seven and a half cents (Box-folder 123/17)
        - Seven and a half cents reprise (Box-folder 123/17)
        - Sewing machines, Laid in: violin B part (Box-folder 123/18)
        - Sleeptite (Box-folder 123/19)
        - Slow down (Box-folder 123/20)
        - Small talk (Box-folder 123/21)
        - Small talk incidental (Box-folder 123/21)
        - Steam heat (Box-folder 123/22)
        - There once was a man (Box-folder 123/23)
        - Think of the time I save (Box-folder 123/24)
    - Pal Joey, 1952 revival, Music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Do it the hard way (Box-folder 84/5)
        - The flower garden of my heart (Box-folder 84/6)
        - Happy hunting horn (Box-folder 84/7)
        - I could write a book (Box-folder 84/8)
        - I'm talking to my pal (Box-folder 84/9)
        - Plant you now, dig you later (Box-folder 84/10)
        - You musn't kick it around (Box-folder 84/11)
    - Park Avenue, 1946, Music by Arthur Schwartz, lyrics by Ira Gershwin
      - Land of opportunitee, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 84/12)
    - Polonaise, 1945, Music by Bronislau Kaper (from Chopin), lyrics by John LaTouche
      - Finale Act I, Short score (Box-folder 84/13)
    - The ragtime blues, circa 1978-1980, Music by Scott Joplin (adapted by Walker), book and lyrics by Mitchell Douglas; Unproduced
      - Fragment of incidental, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 84/14)
      - Early lyric material/notes (Box-folder 84/15)
      - First draft script; notes (Box-folder 84/16)
      - Easy winners, Piano-vocal score; Incomplete (Box-folder 84/16)
      - Script; 1978 Dec. 27 (Box-folder 84/17)
      - Script; 1979 Jan. (Box-folder 84/18)
      - Script; 1979 Mar. 2 (Box-folder 84/19)
      - Script, new version; 1979 Nov. 2, Incomplete; Laid in: letter (Box-folder 85/1)
      - Script; 1979 Dec. 20, Laid in: letter (Box-folder 85/2)
      - Script; 1980 Jan. 12 (Box-folder 85/3)
      - Script; 1980 Jan. 18 (Box-folder 85/4)
      - Running order/master order (Box-folder 85/5)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 85/6)
    - The red mill, 1958 television version, Music by Victor Herbert, lyrics by Henry Blossom
      - Mignonette, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 85/7)
    - Ruff-neck, 1932, Music and lyrics by Bickley Reichner, Don Walker, Joseph F. Follmann, Jr.; Mask and Wig Club show at the University of Pennsylvania
      - Full scores
        - Ballet-hoo (Box-folder 85/8)
        - Bally-hooey vocal (Box-folder 85/9)
        - Entre act (Box-folder 85/10)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 85/11)
        - Finale Act II (Box-folder 85/12)
        - A five year plan for two (Box-folder 123/25)
        - A five year plan for two dance (Box-folder 85/13)
        - A five year plan for two vocal (Box-folder 85/13)
        - A five year plan for two dance more (Box-folder 85/14)
        - Good queen Bess (Box-folder 85/15)
        - Indian dance (Box-folder 85/16)
        - An Indian fantasie, Laid in: short score/sketch (Box-folder 85/17)
        - Just croon (Box-folder 85/18)
        - Lizzie's gigolo dance (Box-folder 85/19)
        - Lizzie's gigolo vocal (Box-folder 85/19)
        - Love in the ruff (Box-folder 123/26)
        - Love in the ruff dance (Box-folder 85/20)
        - Love in the ruff tag second ending (Box-folder 85/20)
        - Love in the ruff vocal (Box-folder 85/20)
        - Opening chorus-archers and guilds (Box-folder 85/21)
        - Opening chorus-archers reprise (Box-folder 85/21)
        - Opening chorus-lords and ladies (Box-folder 85/22)
        - Overture (Box-folder 85/23)
        - Rally 'round Raleigh (Box-folder 85/24)
        - That happy ending (Box-folder 86/1)
        - There's life in the old girl yet (Box-folder 86/2)
        - This is the life vocal and dance (Box-folder 86/3)
        - We are the guards (Box-folder 86/4)
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Bally-hooey (Box-folder 86/5)
        - Doing the hotsy dance (Box-folder 86/6)
        - A five year plan for two (Box-folder 86/7)
        - Good queen Bess (Box-folder 86/8)
        - Just croon (Box-folder 86/9)
        - Lizzie's gigolo (Box-folder 86/10)
        - Love in the ruff (Box-folder 86/11)
        - Opening chorus-Act I (Box-folder 86/12)
        - Opening chorus-have you heard (Box-folder 86/13)
        - Rally 'round Raleigh (Box-folder 86/14)
        - That happy ending, Piano score (Box-folder 86/15)
        - There's life in the old girl yet (Box-folder 86/16)
        - This is the life (Box-folder 86/17)
        - We are the guards (Box-folder 86/18)
      - Parts
        - A five year plan for two (Box-folder 86/19)
      - Non-musical items
        - Libretto, Scenario by Albert G. Miller, book by Beaumont Bruestle (Box-folder 86/20)
        - Souvenir program (Box-folder 86/21)
    - Shenandoah, 1975, Music by Gary Geld, lyrics by Peter Udell
      - Scores–electric keyboard, banjo/guitar, drums, piano/celeste, bass
        - Change to church (Box-folder 87/1)
        - Finale Act I sequence (Box-folder 87/2)
        - Finale coda/ultimo see Pass the cross to me
        - Freedom (Box-folder 87/3)
        - If I were you (Box-folder 87/4)
        - It's a boy! parts I-III (Box-folder 87/5)
        - I've heard it all before (Box-folder 87/6)
        - Meditation I and II (Box-folder 87/7)
        - My little girl (Box-folder 87/8)
        - Next to lovin' (I like fightin') (Box-folder 87/9)
        - The only home I know (Box-folder 87/10)
        - The only home I know reprise (Box-folder 87/11)
        - Opening fanfare, Full score (Box-folder 87/12)
        - Papa's gonna make it alright (Box-folder 87/13)
        - Pass the cross to me/Finale coda/Finale ultimo (Box-folder 87/14)
        - Pass the crossover (Box-folder 87/14)
        - The pickers are comin' (Box-folder 87/15)
        - The pickers are comin' change (Box-folder 87/15)
        - The pickers are comin' ending (Box-folder 87/15)
        - Raise the flag of Dixie parts I-III (Box-folder 87/16)
        - To Jenny's bedroom (Box-folder 87/17)
        - Violets and silverbells (wedding scene) (Box-folder 87/18)
        - Violets and silverbells reprise (Box-folder 87/18)
        - We make a beautiful pair (Box-folder 87/19)
        - Why am I me? (Box-folder 87/20)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 87/21)
        - Lead sheets organized as piano-vocal score, p. 7-46 (Box-folder 87/22)
      - Parts
        - Guitar (Box-folder 87/23-24)
        - Drums (Box-folder 88/1-2)
        - Bass (Box-folder 88/3-4)
        - Transparencies (Box-folder 88/5-6)
    - Stars in your eyes, 1939, Music by Arthur Schwartz, lyrics by Dorothy Fields
      - All the time; Vocal arrangement for Act II ballet, Piano-vocal score/vocal arrangement (Box-folder 88/7)
      - Just a little bit more, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 88/8)
      - This is it, Piano-vocal score/vocal arrangement (Box-folder 88/9)
      - This is it encore, Full score, piano-vocal score/vocal arrangement (Box-folder 88/10)
    - Sweet mistress see Mistress of the inn
    - Top banana, 1951, Music and lyrics by Johnny Mercer, book by H.S. Kraft
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Ambiguous (Box-folder 89/1)
        - I fought every step of the way, Laid in: lyric sheet (Box-folder 89/2)
        - Man of the year (Box-folder 89/3)
        - My home is in my shoes (Box-folder 89/4)
        - My home is in my shoes-section II dance, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 89/4)
        - Nobody understands me (Box-folder 89/5)
        - O.K. for T.V. (Box-folder 89/6)
        - Sans souci (Box-folder 89/7)
        - Senorita Diaz (Box-folder 89/8)
        - Step to the rear of the car, please (Box-folder 89/9)
        - That's for sure (Box-folder 89/10)
        - You're so beautiful-that (Box-folder 89/11)
      - Script (Box-folder 89/12)
    - Touch and go, 1949, Music by Jay Gorney, lyrics by Jean and Walter Kerr
      - Glorious! Atkinson times, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 89/13)
      - Glorious! Atkinson times-new version dance, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 89/13)
    - Twenty-three skidoo see Go fight city hall
    - Up in Central Park, 1945, Music by Sigmund Romberg, lyrics by Dorothy Fields
      - Full scores
        - The big back yard encore (Box-folder 89/14)
        - Close as pages in a book (Box-folder 89/15)
        - When you walk in the room (Box-folder 89/14)
    - U.S.S. Pinafore or "Not tonight, Josephine!" see Memphis bound
    - The vamp, 1955, Alternate title: Delilah; Music by James Mundy, lyrics by John LaTouche
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Back home where I come from (Box-folder 89/17)
        - Flickers intro (Box-folder 89/18)
        - The impossible she (Box-folder 89/19)
        - Opening/Curtain music (Box-folder 89/20)
        - Overture intro, Full score; p. 1-3 (Box-folder 89/21)
        - Scarecrow dance (Box-folder 89/22)
        - Who needs love (Box-folder 89/23)
        - Without you (Box-folder 89/24)
        - Yeemy, yeemy (Box-folder 89/25)
        - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 89/26)
      - Notes (Box-folder 89/27)
    - Wicked, wicked city see Go fight city hall
    - Wish you were here, 1952, Music and lyrics by Harold Rome
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Ballad of a social director (Box-folder 90/1)
        - Camp Karefree song (Box-folder 90/2)
        - Could be (Box-folder 90/3)
        - Don Jose of far Rockaway (Box-folder 90/4)
        - Everybody loves everybody (Box-folder 90/5)
        - Flattery (Box-folder 90/6)
        - Glimpse of love (Box-folder 90/7)
        - Goodbye love (Box-folder 90/8)
        - High and mighty (Box-folder 90/9)
        - Look at me! (Box-folder 90/10)
        - Mix and mingle (Box-folder 90/11)
        - Relax! (Box-folder 90/12)
        - Shopping around (Box-folder 90/13)
        - Such a nice girl! (Lament for Teddy Stern) (Box-folder 90/14)
        - Summer afternoon (Box-folder 90/15)
        - Teddy Stern (Box-folder 90/16)
        - They won't know me! (Box-folder 90/17)
        - Tripping the light fantastic (Box-folder 90/18)
        - Waiters song (Box-folder 90/19)
        - Where did the night go? (Box-folder 90/20)
        - Wish you were here (Box-folder 90/21)
        - Piano-conductor score, Inscribed to Don Walker from Harold Rome (Box-folder 90/22)
    - You never know, 1952, Music and lyrics by Cole Porter; This is a collection of Cole Porter songs from various shows, apparently being considered for a new adaption of his show with the same title; there were other songs included with these which were not retained, as they were un-annotated copies of published sheet music, whereas the items here include manuscripts by Albert Sirmay, and several scores that appear to have been annotated by Porter himself; there is an undated program for You Never Know at the Grist Mill Playhouse in Andover, New Jersey (undated), that was the apparent production that these scores were being used to prepare for.
      - Titles of piano-vocal scores: All I’ve got to get now is my man; Could it be you; Fresh as a daisy; From now on; Hail Bibinski; I hate you darling; I’m throwing a ball tonight; Still got my health; Just one of those things; The leader of a big time band; Let’s do it; Only another boy and girl; There must be some one for me; What a ball; When my baby goes to town; Where did the nights go; Why shouldn’t I? Wow-ooh-wolf; You do something to me, Laid in: program, songlisting and notes, lyric sheets (Box-folder 90/23-24)
    - Your hit parade, circa 1957, Music and lyrics by Don Walker; Radio program
      - The music that got away: The survey song, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 91/1)
      - Opening billboard part I instrumental, Piano score (Box-folder 91/2)
      - Opening I, Short score with vocals (Box-folder 91/2)
      - Opening billboard part II instrumental, Piano score (Box-folder 91/3)
      - Hit parade opening #2 (Tony), Short score with vocals (Box-folder 91/2)
    - Zorba, 1968, Music by John Kander, lyrics by Fred Ebb
      - Full scores
        - After butterfly (Box-folder 124/1)
        - Bell dance (Box-folder 124/2)
        - The bend in the road (Box-folder 124/3)
        - Boom-boom for you (Box-folder 124/4)
        - Boubalina (Box-folder 124/5)
        - Boubalina change (Box-folder 124/6)
        - Bows part I (Box-folder 124/7)
        - Bows part II (Box-folder 124/8)
        - Broken record (Box-folder 124/9)
        - The butterfly (Box-folder 124/10)
        - The butterfly intro (Box-folder 124/11)
        - Canavaro to Khania (Box-folder 124/12)
        - The crow (Box-folder 124/13)
        - The crow change (Box-folder 124/14)
        - Entracte (Box-folder 124/15)
        - Entrance of Zorba and Nikos (Box-folder 124/16)
        - Exit march (Box-folder 125/1)
        - Exit-Zorba and Nikos (Box-folder 125/2)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 125/3)
        - The first time (Box-folder 125/4)
        - Goodbye Canavaro (Box-folder 125/5)
        - Happy birthday (Box-folder 125/6)
        - I am free (Box-folder 125/7)
        - Khania parts I-IV (Box-folder 125/8)
        - Life is (Box-folder 125/9)
        - Life is sequel (Box-folder 125/10)
        - Look at the fields (Box-folder 125/11)
        - Mimiko (Box-folder 125/12)
        - The mine (Box-folder 125/13)
        - Nikos-window incidental (Box-folder 126/1)
        - No boom-boom (Box-folder 126/2)
        - Only love (Box-folder 126/3)
        - Prologue (Box-folder 126/4)
        - Sousta (Box-folder 126/5)
        - That's a beginning (why can't I speak?) (Box-folder 126/6)
        - The top of the hill (Box-folder 126/7)
        - Vive la difference (Box-folder 126/8)
        - Why can't I speak? (Box-folder 126/9)
        - Women, p. 5-6 only; dated 1983 Jan. 28 and 1983 May 17 (Box-folder 126/10)
        - Women's march (Box-folder 126/11)
        - Y'assou (Box-folder 126/12)
        - Y'assou change (Box-folder 126/13)
        - Zorba's dance (Box-folder 126/14)
        - Zorba dance II/new ending, p. 7-10 only (Box-folder 126/14)
        - Miscellaneous music and notes (Box-folder 126/15)
      - Piano-conductor scores
        - Bows part II (Box-folder 91/4)
        - The first time (Box-folder 91/5)
        - Goodbye Canavaro (Box-folder 91/6)
        - I am free (Box-folder 91/7)
        - Murder scene, Lead sheets (Box-folder 91/8)
        - Zorba's dance number 2 (Box-folder 91/9)
      - Parts, incomplete
        - I am free (Box-folder 91/10)
        - No boom boom, Recording arrangement (Box-folder 91/11)
        - Only love (Box-folder 91/12)
        - Zorba's dance (Box-folder 91/13)
        - Bouzouki (Box-folder 91/14)
        - Electric harpsichord (Box-folder 91/15)
        - Violins (Box-folder 91/16)
        - Miscellaneous music, Not related to Zorba, but found with it; Most of this material appears to be piano scores for a film score, and a piano-conductor score medley titled “USO walk without you –trio” of “I don’t want to walk without you.” “Roseanna” and “I wish I didn’t love you so,” arranged by Billy Byers (Box-folder 91/17)
  - Non-Show Music (Box 92-106, 127-131)
    - Alone together, Notes (Box-folder 92/1)
    - America, America, Sketch combining "America" and "Yankee Doodle" (Box-folder 92/2)
    - Annie get your gun, Piano-vocal scores; Annotated scores: Doin' what comes natur'lly; Who do you love I hope; You can't get a man with a gun (Box-folder 92/3)
    - Anniversary song, Full score (Box-folder 92/4)
    - Are you makin' any money?, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 92/5)
    - Are you sure?, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 92/6)
    - L'arlesienne suite no. II, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 92/7)
    - Auld lang syne, Vocal arrangement/sketch; Corner torn off (Box-folder 92/8)
    - Bali ha'i, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 92/9)
    - Ballad #1; Ballad #6; Ballad #7, Piano scores (Box-folder 92/10)
    - Ballroom duet and ensemble, Short score (Box-folder 92/11)
    - Ballroom duo and ensemble, Full score; Incomplete (Box-folder 92/11)
    - Band I (Stockholm), Full score (Box-folder 92/12)
    - Be like a leaf; Be like a leaf in the wind #1; Be like a leaf in the wind #2, Piano-vocal score, piano scores; No lyric (Box-folder 92/13)
    - Be-gone my love, Piano-vocal scores, negative photostat score for small orchestra, photostat full score; Music by Margaret Hopkins, lyrics by Don Walker (Box-folder 92/14)
    - Beautiful lady, Short score (Box-folder 92/15)
    - Begin the beguine, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 92/16)
    - Big military intro, Sketch (Box-folder 92/17)
    - Blow me down, Vocal arrangement/short score (Box-folder 92/18)
    - Blues #1, Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 92/19)
    - Bodoni county, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 92/20)
    - A break in the clouds, Piano-vocal score, lyric sheet (Box-folder 92/21)
    - Buckle down, Winsocki, Short score (Box-folder 92/22)
    - Burning leaves, Piano scores, lead sheet, lyric sheet; Music by Don Walker (Box-folder 92/23)
    - Can't escape from you, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 92/24)
    - Careless love, Sketch (Box-folder 92/25)
    - Cavatina from Figaro, Full score, negative photostat (Box-folder 92/26)
    - Cheek to cheek, Full score (Box-folder 130/1)
    - Chicken reel, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 92/27)
    - Chinese lullaby, Score for violin, saxes, gong, bass and cello (Box-folder 92/28)
    - Chloe, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 92/29)
    - Clarinet concert; Clarinet concerto I, Scores/sketches (Box-folder 92/30)
    - College songs
      - College medley #1, Short score/sketch; Laid in: original folder (Box-folder 92/31)
      - College medley #2, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 92/32)
      - Illinois (loyalty march), Sketch (Box-folder 92/33)
      - Last chorus collegiate, Short score (Box-folder 92/34)
      - Michigan (the victors), Full score (Box-folder 92/35)
      - Ohio state, Sketch (Box-folder 92/36)
      - Pitt (University of Pittsburgh), Full score (Box-folder 92/37)
      - Stein song, Full score (Box-folder 92/38)
      - Comin' thru the rye, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 93/1)
      - Cover girl medley, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 93/2)
      - Cover girl intro, Short score with vocals (Box-folder 93/2)
      - La cumparsita, Parts for tango orchestra (Box-folder 93/3)
      - Czech medley, Short score with vocal, negative photostat; No lyric (Box-folder 93/4)
      - Dance, don't run to the nearest exit, Lead sheet (Box-folder 93/5)
      - Dange melange, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 93/6)
      - Agnes de Mille Dance Theatre, circa 1953, Unless otherwise noted, the folders below contain a full score, piano-conductor score, and string parts; some of the full scores appear to be in the hand of Hans Spialek
        - Ballet class (Box-folder 93/7)
        - The banjo (Box-folder 93/8)
        - Brigadoon
          - Come to me (Box-folder 93/9)
          - Drunk scene (Box-folder 93/10)
          - Fight scene (Box-folder 93/11)
          - Funeral dance, Short score; Incomplete, parts only (Box-folder 93/12)
          - Opening (Box-folder 93/13)
          - Sword dance (Box-folder 93/14)
          - Wedding dance (Box-folder 93/15)
        - Bumble-bee in a garden (Box-folder 94/1)
        - Cherry tree legend (Box-folder 94/2-4)
        - Clipper sailing (Box-folder 94/5)
        - Conversations pleasant and unpleasant (overture) (Box-folder 94/6-8)
        - Gala performance, Piano-conductor score not included (Box-folder 95/1)
        - Hares on the mountains
          - Short score (Box-folder 95/2)
          - Parts (Box-folder 95/2)
        - Kansas city stomp
          - Full score (Box-folder 127/1)
          - Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 95/4)
        - May day (Box-folder 95/5)
        - Nelson (Box-folder 95/6)
        - Paint your wagon
          - Can of beans, Full score, parts; Incomplete (Box-folder 95/7)
          - Coach dance, Full score, parts; Incomplete (Box-folder 95/8)
          - Finale, Full score, parts; Incomplete (Box-folder 95/9)
          - Horsing around, Full score, parts; Incomplete (Box-folder 95/10)
          - Lonely men, Full score, parts; Incomplete (Box-folder 95/11)
          - Night scene, Full score, parts; Incomplete (Box-folder 95/12)
          - Rope dance, Full score, parts; Incomplete (Box-folder 95/13)
          - Rumson town (Box-folder 95/14)
          - They call the wind Maria (Box-folder 96/1)
          - Transition to coach dance (Box-folder 96/2)
          - Wandering star, night scene (Box-folder 96/3)